hello guys atom likeo uh here
um I was one of the I guess I was the 8th cubson out in Germany
the first one in Dortmund and we have uh in December from the 9th to
from the 1st to 9th
a cyber week is the biggest deals of the year so yeah
if you're having still having education budget left
so feel free to spend it in a really nice way
Hallo liebe community Arthur Meiko hier äh
ich war glaube ich der Achte künstler in Deutschland
der Erste in Dortmund und äh ich
Ich Hab news für euch
wir haben ne Cyber Week vom ersten Dezember bis zum neunten Dezember
das heißt ähm Das ist der biggest deal des jahres
das heißt wenn ihr noch bisschen education budget übrig habt
und eigentlich wisst was IHR mit eurer zeit macht
dann viel free
leute Holt euch die deals oder schaut auch halt auch schau danach
das wird sehr sehr cool ich nutze es auch das heißt danke schön
hi I'm Christophe Sotier
I'm the training and certification lead for the CNCF
and I just want to remind you that Cyber Week is around the corner
December 1st to 9th it will be the biggest deal of the year
so it's the great opportunity for you to become a couponer
or a Golden Couponer
and get all the benefits and be part of this amazing community
and be recognized for all your knowledge so please remind that
Bonjour c'est Christophe Sotier
j'suis le training certification lead du SNCF euh
je voulais juste vous rappeler que LA cyber week
euh est toute proche de décembre
du premier décembre au neuf décembre
CE sont les plus grosses offres de l'année donc
profitez de cette occasion
pour devenir un cube astronaute OU un golden cube Astronaute
et accéder à tous les bénéfices
que vous offre de faire partie de cette Grande communauté et
c'est un Bon moyen de faire reconnaître vos connaissances
Hi, my name is Christopher Tineo.
I'm a Kubestronaut from the Latin American communities.
I want to remind you that if you haven’t certified yet,
this is the best time of the year
because now we have the Cyber Week from December 1 to December 9
and we're gonna have the biggest deals of the year, so start now!
hello guys I'm Fabricius Gura
Cubs run out going for golden and 1st duty cyber week
note December from 1 to 9 before Christmas
then you can have your presents
the these are the biggest deals of the year in training certifications
learning spreading
becoming better in knowledge not just because of us
but because of you that you can learn from the new technologies
and what about the certification programs and the training
why they are important I am 54
I'm old but the last year on September
I did the cubes run out in 30 days
and I presented that at the presentation at Cubecon London
proudly not just because I did it in 30 days
but because I Learned a lot and it was 30 days of fantastic experience
you have to it's important to demonstrate yourself that you can grow
and then when you will have these jackets
everyone here at the cubcon will tell you who you are
I want to meet you please come here
it will be fantastic so please sign up the LFX
take all the free courses
it's enormous a huge amount of courses
and become like us expert in what you like to do
so you will become a solution partner for people
and not just for companies
you will not be hired because of your expertise
but because of your knowledge
Ciao ragazzi qui fabrizio sguara Io non vivo più in Italia
da un Po di tempo vivo ormai in Sud America
Dal duemila e sette però sono
qui al cubecon sono stato con tanti italiani
e voglio darvi UN messaggio personale prima di tutto il dovere
c'è UN cyber week di in dicembre Dal dall'1 al 9
dove CI sono questi in Inglese
Lo dico biggest deals of the year
cioè possiamo prenderci queste occasioni
meravigliose andate sul sito della LFX e controllate
quali sono I percorsi di studio eccetera
eccetera
diventeremo migliori però Io ho fatto questo
questo programma mi sono certificato
adesso sto facendo il golden
perché Lo faccio a cinquantaquattro anni
potrei fare Qualcos'altro andare a spalare LA neve da qualche parte
anche se in Sud America non si spala molta
neve diciamo che LA cosa importante in questo mondo è imparare
essere al tempo continuare a fare quello che ci piace
cioè Tecnologia sono sicuro al cento per cento
che in Italia CI sono molte opportunità per imparare e rappresentare
il nostro paese all'estero
come possiamo realmente fare con LA testa
che abbiamo ragazzi qui CI sono tanti italiani
che creano bisogna essere migliori nel percorso di studio
non è solo universitario è anche personale
e sono sicuro che tutti voi Potete fare realmente un Gran
un grande passo avanti con questo tipo di certificazioni
e questo programma VI aspetto al prossimo cubecon e a Amsterdam
andiamo
lì ci facciamo una Gita per LA città ci sono tante opportunità
CI vediamo tutti insieme
e facciamo un gruppo di cubo
astronauti italiani più in Alto
ancora di quello che già è un saluto a tutti
hey everyone my name is Hadi and I am one of the golden cube snouts
and the Cyber week is coming from December 1st till December 9th
all biggest deals are coming
all the biggest deal of the year are coming
if you want to become golden QS nut
if you want to become QS nut
or if you want to start your journey
with Linux Foundation certification
go for it this is the time
take the advantage good luck
hey everyone Cyber Week is coming up December the first to the 9th
the biggest deals of the year
so if you're actually looking to become a cube astronaut
now's the perfect time
hello Cyber Week is here from December 1st to 9
so if you're trying to get CKA
CKD or any Linux any Kubeneti certification
these are the biggest deals of the year
hello my name is Pedro Celeston
I am an SCF ambassador and a Golden Cube astronaut
I'm here to remind you of the Cyber Week that's coming in December
from 1st to 9th don't miss the biggest deals of the year
olá a todos
EU sou o Pedro Celestin sou o embaixador da CNCF e Golden Cross
Ronald estou aqui para lembrá los da cyber week
de primeiro de dezembro a nove de dezembro
onde teremos as melhores promoções do ano
os treinamentos da CNCF e certificações obrigado
hey guys this is Ramesh from Cube Khan
Cyber Week is coming up December 1st to December 9
biggest deal forever go and get the Cube Khan
go and get the golden cube Khan don't miss it
hi my name is Ronaldo Linares
I am a principal cloud engineer
and if you wanted to get into Kubernetes
certification is the way to go
it gives you a structured way to learn the technology
and there's a lot of stuff out there
and if you don't take the time to get that certification
you're gonna get lost in all of the information so focus
take one certification it'll give you a structure to post
to learn it and that way
you'll be
able to now help promote this type of information out to the industry
now for you to get your certifications on on the Cheap
Cyber Week December 1 through the 9th
biggest deals of the year you make
you don't want to miss it take care
what what we've actually found with the exact